

#### **PROFILE**

An ordinary person with extraordinary goals, equipped with unique & optimistic perception. Pursuing MBA with aim to become a Senior Manager or Consultant Administration in а well-known organization in next five years. Served as President of National Student Council Pakistan. Overall 7 years of experience in Administration, Project Management, Planning, Training & Learning domain including international experience in Nepal.

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

#### KIRAN FOUNDATION:

- Designed adoptable policies and rules for the betterment of the organization.
- Reduce and save petty cash from 50,000 per month to 32,000 per month by handling efficiently.
- with In-Lined staff company's objective by delivering back to back different In-house training sessions.
- Designed time saving transport route for official vehicle.

#### **MARKAZ-E-UMEED:**

- Develop new and easy formats of internal documentation.
- Execution of CCTV camera to ensuring security of premises.
- Organized first annual event Social Expo.
- Provide extensive traininas administration and operational staff for the betterment of the organization.

# ATA REHMAN ZAKI

ADMINISTRATION AND MANAGEMENT EXPERT



## EDUCATION

EDUCATION	INSTITUTION	YEAR OF PASSING
MBA – (Weekend)	IQRA University	Final Year
B.A – Social Science	University of Karachi	2016
FSC – (Pre-Engg)	Govt. Degree College for Boys North Karachi	2010
SSC – (Comp-Sci)	Cantab Grammar School	2008

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **KIRAN FOUNDATION - MANAGER OPERATIONS (DCTO Campus)**

DEC 2016-PRESENT

Design and implement Admin related strategies, plans and procedures. Oversee maintenance, repair, utility operations, and security of the campus. Coordinate with vendors for purchasing materials for organization. Responsible for cost saving initiatives and maintaining of petty cash efficiently. Responsible to manage & supervise inventory of the campus. Oversee of maintenance of all sports area and equipment including cricket, football, archery, chess, table tennis and other indoor games. Oversee and manage all sports events within the campus. Oversee and ensure health and safety environment within the campus. Provide training to administration/operations staff. Dealing with security & government institutions regarding any legal matter. Work closely with HR, Finance, academic & program staff to oversee all aspect of administration, logistic & coordination for the campus. Manage events and programs. Develop & maintain official data base.

#### MARKAZ-E-UMEED - ADMINISTRATION OFFICER

FEB 2014 - NOV 2016

Oversee all administrative activities. Responsible to execution of all the sports, cultural and development related program, Responsible to maintenance, repair, utility operations, and security of the school. Communicate effectively and regularly with staff, students, and parents through regular meetings, one-one interactions. Ensure safety and security of all students/staff while they are on the school premises. Manage office supplies stock and place orders. Work as event manager of social expo (every year) at expo center Karachi



# INTERNATIONAL WORK EXPERINCE

## **AIESEC EXCHANGE PROGRAM**

SEPT 2016 - OCT 2016

Attended four weeks Exchange Program as AIESEC Global Volunteer at Kathmandu, Nepal. Where I worked with BEHANI Enterprise as **Business Administration Consultant.** 

#### **CONTACT DETAILS**

#### PHONE:

+92-300-8976159 +92-336-5726953

#### ADDERESS:

R-1589/14, Federal B' Area, Near Galaxy Food Point, Karachi.

#### **EMAIL:**

arzee.official@gmail.com

### **HOBBIES/INTEREST**

- Read Newspapers/Articles
- Write Food Blogs
- Archery at club
- Swimming at club
- Explore Cities/Places

#### **SKILLS**

- ✓ Leadership
- ✓ Planning & Designing
- ✓ Human & Interpersonal
- ✓ Communication & Dealing
- ✓ Cost Saving
- ✓ Negotiation
- ✓ Problem solving
- ✓ Decision making
- √ IT & Computer

# WORKSHOPS & TRAININGS ATTENDED

- In House Four Months Training Program on Health & Safety Environment within the premises by Mr. Naeem (Expert HSE) at Kiran Foundation. (In Progress)
- Online Certificate Course Let's Break the Chain of COVID-19
   Infection by Community Immunity Ambassador Program of the Mohammed Bin Rashid University (MBRU) in April 2020.
- One Day Workshop on Transformation Communication, Team Work & Attitude by Torque Corp at Mövenpick Hotel – Karachi in Oct 2019.
- One Day Workshop on Managing Difficult Behaviors by Let's Educate at Karachi in Oct 2019.
- Three Days Workshop on Train the Trainer by State Bank of Pakistan at SBP Head Office – Karachi in June 2019.
- Two Days Workshop on **Blogging & Articles** by **Rutgers Pakistan** at **Islamabad** in June 2018.
- Four Days Workshop on Organizational Development by Community World Service Asia at Murree in May 2016.
- Three Days Young Leader Camp by Pakistan US Alumni Network at Kashmir in March 2015
- Four Days Workshop on Youth Leadership and Professional Development by Young Social Reformers at Karachi in June 2011.

## E MEMBERSHIP & CLUBS

PRESIDENT SOUTH at SINDH ARCHERY ASSOCIATION DEC 2019 – PRESENT

## **MEMBER at WWF**

MARCH 2017 - APRIL 2018

MEMBER at YOUTH PARLIAMENT OF PAKISTAN

JAN 2015 - DEC 2016